elitedeals.com 2017-12-15

# Privacy Policy

_This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, orderingsystem, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information butmay only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this storethrough Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects informationabout your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/details.html) for moreinformation about how Yahoo! uses this information._

 ** _EliteDeals.com Privacy Policy_**

EliteDeals.com is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and the order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the Yahoo! Privacy Policy for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information.  
**  
We will never sell, trade, or rent any customer or gift recipient e-mail address or personal information to any third party.** Nor will we share this information with any third party except to the extent necessary to fulfill an order or when the outside party is strictly acting on our behalf with no independent right to use the information we provide. We may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to certain reputable third party vendors but these statistics will not include any identifying personal information. We may disclose personal information in the event that if we are required by law however. Accordingly, you authorize us to disclose any and all information about you to law enforcement or other governmental official as we deem necessary or appropriate with any investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, piracy, or other unlawful activity that is illegal and that may expose us to legal liability.

Our order form collects customer contact information such as name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, and credit card financial information needed to process and bill an order. We take numerous precautions to protect customer information and the sensitive information that is submitted to us is protected both online and offline.

The contact information is necessary to personalize and send information about orders to our customers, to fulfill and notify you of delivery, and to get in touch with you if necessary for customer service or questions about an order. We may also use customer information and the Internet Protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet to improve the content of our site, to improve your shopping experience, and for marketing and promotional purposes.

We also collect contact information about gift recipients to ensure correct gift delivery. We may send special offers and information about new items or features to our valued customers and gift recipients from time to time. The recipient may always opt out of receiving future mailings.  
Customers may join our mailing list by choosing to register on our home page or during the checkout process. You can contact us to unsubscribe and we will remove your name and e-mail address from any future mailings. A page of our site is forwarded to the specified e-mail recipient only when you use the Refer-a-Friend feature on our site.

EliteDeals.com does not use cookies to track customer movement on our site. However, Yahoo! uses cookies to facilitate the checkout process. Please see the Yahoo! Privacy Policy. You may still make purchases at our site if you have set your browser to disable cookies but functionality may be limited.

* * *

**_Security_**

We understand and share your concern about security and privacy. It is reassuring to know that it is statistically safer to use your credit card on the web than to use it in a store or restaurant. The information that you provide when placing an order with us (e.g. your name, address, and credit card information) is secure. It cannot be read or tampered with during transmission.

EliteDeals.com is hosted by Yahoo! Store on its secure servers and our orders are processed using their shopping cart. Our checkout process uses industry standard SSL (Secure Socket Layer) technology to encrypt and scramble all personal information including your name, address, and credit card information so that it may not be read by others as it travels over the Internet. Secure Socket Layer encryption is employed during checkout when the URL in browsers, such as Microsoft Internet Explorer and Netscape Navigator, changes from "http" to "https". The "s" indicates that you are in a secure area. Your browser may also show a pop-up window when you are here.

For your security, we authorize your credit card after we obtain confirmation that your card is a valid number and has not been reported lost or stolen. We also verify that the "Bill To" address matches the address on the credit card used. It is not uncommon for a request for credit card authorization to fail at times. We will contact you if we experience such difficulties and you may wish to provide another credit card.

Email is not encrypted so please do not transmit your credit card number via e-mail.

Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, the maximum amount that your bank can require you pay for any fraudulent charge on your credit card is up to $50. Notify your credit card company immediately should you ever suspect a fraudulent charge on your credit card as you would for any other unauthorized charge.
